testing Ai generate subs, please disable if uncomfortable. warning is removed at 0:15
Hi
Flo-hi
Today
I'm not super
hungry but I'm a bit peckish
so
I was going to have a late-night snack
and thought I should
eat it with Flover
so I turned on the live
Today's late-night snack menu is
Cup Noodle
I really want to eat ramen
but we have a concert to do
But honestly Cup Noodle
is really delicious
It kind of satisfies the craving
I did eat dinner
I ate dinner but
I was craving
this again
So I
debated if I should eat the Malatang flavor
since I haven't tried it
I thought about it
and just went with the spicy flavor
It's so good
Actually I
was originally going to wash up and sleep
so I took my contacts out
I regretted it
because I suddenly wanted to do a live
I could have looked a bit prettier
I could have looked a lot prettier
I only look a little pretty
Baby come here
Come here
What happened
Why did you bark
Yeah tell mom
Why did you bark just now
What's wrong
You surprised me
It's okay
Mom will protect you
Where did your snack go
Where did your snack go get it
get it
Where did your snack go it's on the table
Get it
Yeah
He brought his snack he really understands well right
I'm telling you he's basically human
He went to the room and brought his snack
He's seriously smarter than me
Baby come eat over here
Eat
Eat eat want me to lay this down for you
I'll lay something nice down for you
He's an aristocratic dog
so
he only eats on top of a blanket like this
Am I eating Rosé Buldak
Carbo
Not Rosé but Carbo Carbo Buldak
But I only eat Carbo Buldak
when I go overseas
And since there are Flovers who want to see our Huji I'll do this
He keeps going behind me
When I go overseas I crave spicy food a lot since there's a lot of greasy
food so I kind of
crave spicy food the spicy taste
The doll is scary
But
everyone who sees it says it looks scary
It's cute though
It doesn't move
That one is
a doll I got
when I went on a trip to Europe
a European man
made by hand
I was walking down the street
and it was so cute
so I bought it
He even gave me a discount
But it's too close right
It's a bit burdensome right
He's working hard to hide his snack right now
Who are you
hiding this from
Me
Are you afraid I'll eat it
You eat it all
I won't steal it
Wow
I really think I need to eat one more
It's so good
But has anyone ever eaten Cup Noodle
and then eaten real ramen
You eat Cup Noodle
and it doesn't satisfy you
so you become completely sure you need to eat real ramen
It's not just me right
Ah it really is delicious
and then
you eat ramen
It always gives me
conviction
Ramen is truly delicious
Honestly last night
I really wanted a late-night snack
but we had a public fansign today
I really felt like I shouldn't eat
Since today
I have to look pretty
for Flover and also
because a lot of people
were coming to see us
I felt like it needed to be a day
with zero
puffiness so I held back a lot
I felt like it needed to be a day
Right I can't hold back now
Mmm today
really
It's time to
cut his hair
Yeah
Right a lot of people really came today I didn't know there would be that many
So I was surprised because so many came
Hey pull my clothes up
I think it's pulled up fine
How do I pull it up like this
They only saw the top of our heads
and left
And for the Flovers who came
to get the fansign today
They found it quite burdensome
So I asked
if they applied without knowing
They said they applied knowing it all
Right
Even though they knew
when they actually got there
there were so many people
so it could be
a bit burdensome
They said it's like a vicarious idol experience
So in between
I told them
to turn around
and take a look at the view
like this
I was like look at the view how is it
but they said they couldn't turn around
because it was too burdensome
But a public fansign for the first time in a while
was really fun
It's a bit spicy right
How is a
12 year age gap
you ask
What do you mean how is it
How should it be
How am I supposed
to think about
someone 12 years younger
You were just born earlier
Yeah you were born just a moment ago
That's what it is
So Flover is 14 years old
You're a middle schooler
It's a very difficult time for you
Wow Huji is already
turning three years old
Time really flies
It's crazy
I really feel like I need to eat one more what do you think
You probably think it's a bad idea right
Ah but it's so good
But I bought snacks today too
Lately I've been into
frozen Jocheong Yugwa Flover
Have you tried freezing Jocheong Yugwa
It's really delicious
Try it
You said that's what my mom eats
What's wrong with
what mothers eat
Why are you being like this
to Jocheong Yugwa
You don't want to go to school tomorrow mmm
You have
to go
You have to do it
You can do it
Going to work is worse
I think I hated going to school more than going to work
Because with going to work
there's a reward
you know
There's a payoff
There's a payoff you receive compensation for the work you do
But
there's no payoff for studying
They just tell you to do it
So it doesn't work out
You know it in your head
but your heart isn't in it
Because it doesn't give me anything immediately
School was so hard for me
But you have friends
You have friends
at work too
It's completely
separate
from that
I guess it's just me then
who has friends
Ah because I have friends I go to work with
But
there are a lot of cases
where people become real best friends
with their coworkers
Like actually going on trips together
That's not very common right
Meeting up on days off too
I'm not really that type either
Because
for me
if you get too close it's hard when working
Because I can't say the things I need to say
So
but then again
there are people
who just
click really well
with you
With people like that
I do kind of want to
go on a date with them but
I haven't been able to yet
And honestly our job
is that they treat us
comfortably
but at the same time
they don't treat us
too casually either
so they are very respectful
which makes it
a bit difficult
I think
Office romance
Office romance could actually be happening
someone might be doing it
someone
No but
it could happen but for me
I don't understand it
Ah Nagyung
Ah that's not office romance
She's not a company employee
Nagyung isn't a company employee
What I mean by company employees is really
working in the office
That kind of
feeling
Ah since we're in the same company
I guess you could look at it that way too
Do they look sexy when giving a briefing or something
How is it
How is your manager
How is your deputy manager
Ah that's so funny ah should I eat snacks again
Doing a live
with Flover
again
is making me want to eat everything
I already finished the Cup Noodle
Ah I'm only wearing pajama pants
so I'll step out like this
My pants shouldn't be seen
I'll sit back down and come in
Ta
da
This is
frozen Jocheong Yugwa
Looks delicious right
I'll let you hear what it sounds like
when you eat it frozen
It's totally
crispy
If you eat it like this
And it's super refreshing
It feels amazing
It's so good
If you aren't careful
you could scrape
the roof of your mouth
You have to eat it carefully
It's so delicious
How long do I freeze it for
I just put this in the freezer
and it's been about
five days
since then
Can I see how many people
are watching the live I can't see it
I can only see
the number of hearts
This is the number of hearts right
102K
Right
It passed 100
The flying chair video on Supa got a ton of views
I'm very proud
The hard work
was definitely worth it
It passed 3 million
Crazy
The short clip has over 10 million
I saw it
I saw that too
on Shorts
saying I'm heavy
and going viral
because I only flew a little bit
But
since it's true that I weigh the most
it probably makes sense that I didn't fly far
Because I'm tall
my weight is
obviously going to be higher
Since the members
have a height difference with me
I didn't lose my confidence though
Why would I lose my confidence
Did Flover lose their confidence
Why would you lose confidence yeah I'm heavy
Did you lose confidence
I'm heavy so why does that make you lose confidence
But
since I
have a bit of a height difference with the members
Right now
I'm maintaining
the mid-to-high 40kg range
but during our off-season
I hit exactly
50kg
But
when I told the members
ah I gained weight
and am eating well
they asked how much I weigh
so I said 50
It's not that much right
but the members
reacted like this
To them a number starting with 5 must be so shocking
Hey members
being 168cm
and 50kg
really isn't weighing
that much
but they were like you don't look like it but you weigh 50kg
Since our members
hit numbers starting with 3 and stuff
50 must have been a very shocking number to them
So
ah to people who are this skinny
the number 50
is a shocking number
I suddenly feel like a giant
Flover
If it's like that I can't promote
Ah since elementary school
I've never seen my weight start with a 3
I haven't seen it since early elementary school
Because I grew up late
And about the water bottle flipping
the water bottle itself
was completely flawed
Isn't it crossing the line to give us ICIS
Honestly they should have given us Samdasoo at least
Yeah
they should have given us the square Samdasoo
bottles
I've never seen anyone do water bottle flipping with ICIS
Seriously
It was all crushed and so round how are you supposed to stand it up
He must be sleepy
Now
he's sleepy so
he's making a spot to sleep right now
He's getting ready to sleep
For me when I eat
this Jocheong Yugwa I get a sugar spike
Then I wash up quickly
since it takes over an hour
I let my food digest during that time
and drying my hair takes an hour and a half
Then
I can just go to sleep right after
Mmm drying my hair takes a really long time
My hair is long you know
Someone washed up in 5 minutes in the army
How do you wash up
in 5 minutes
If you just wash your face
I guess you could wash up
in 5 minutes
Oh
Wait does that mean you wash your face and hair at the same time
Ah your hair is short too right
Even so it seems hard
I guess it works
I'm eating this so deliciously right
Flovers should eat too
The comments today
are super fast
Right
I
earlier
Wait
what was I just going to say
I can't remember sorry
Is Huji fully grown yes Huji is fully grown
He is a fully grown Huji
Why is Huji a snack
I almost
finished the snack
The snack is good
Doesn't this have
a ton inside
It only has a little bit
Ah I'm full
I think the sugar spike
is coming Flover
I had a lot to say
to Flover
but now that I'm here I can't remember
Is this how Flovers feel
when they come to a fansign
Wait it's too fast so
I can't see anything
You want me to do what
I can't find it
It scrolled down way too fast
Are you curious about
promotional behind-the-scenes
or anything like that
Flover
Did I not see Odyssey
I didn't have time today
My favorite hair makeup and styling
For me Inkigayo
the white outfit
with the comma hair
styling
was it
I was really satisfied with that day
Is there a secret to being pretty
There is no secret
I'm pretty because Flovers look at me beautifully
Flovers looking at me
beautifully makes it so
Right
Phew
I want to
sit down
on the blanket
Recently
the Chaeyoungs
came over to my house
Why are you
doing this whenever mom tries to say something
Say hi
Ah you hid your snack here right
Ah sorry
You came to find it where did it go
Oh sorry
I don't think it's here
I wasn't trying to steal it
It's not here
Where did it go
I didn't hide it
Did anyone see where he hid it
No one
Really
It's not here
It's gone baby
You look so panicked
and it's making me panic too
Oh it's over there
It's over there the snack
Yeah it's here come here and eat
What
Oh you want me to lay it down for you
Seriously
whatever
I'm really
frustrated
Because he was sitting on his own thing
he's acting like this to me
He's not even going to eat it but he set the snack down
and is just being greedy for no reason
Seriously
it's so absurd
Where are you going now
Say hi
Is he going
I guess he's going
No no no no
Jelly attack
Chop chop chop
When I mess around
he plays along
My son is playing with me
Wait
Huji is playing with me no way
I'm playing with him
I was just going to say Huji
doesn't bite hard but I have scars everywhere
Ah but it doesn't hurt this is a different scar
He just kind of goes
ang ang ang
like this
He doesn't bite
painfully
just enough to leave a mark
But sometimes
when he gets super excited
he bites hard if he bites me like ang I'll
do this and he immediately
lowers his head
and makes a super sorry
face
Like this
Anyway the Chaeyoungs came over to my house recently for the first time
They came over
and usually
since I meet older unnies I usually go
empty-handed
When I go
I just go
But since they're both younger
I felt like I needed to do something for them
So
I went grocery shopping I basically
went shopping
and I didn't cook myself but
I bought pre-cooked food
I bought cooked food
and served
them
I also made them good coffee to drink
And Chaeyoung's dog
Puding
came over as well
so they played together
and it was really fun
Right the dog that sent a message on From
Did I go to Nagyung's house no I was too tired
so I couldn't go
I'm a bit tired right now too
so I kept debating
if I should go or not
and said let's meet
when we have time
after the concert
is over
I was a bit tired
I should go when my condition is good
and play
Since it hasn't been
officially announced yet
I have to be careful
about talking about it first
If you just wait a bit
you'll find out
What do you mean
is there a concert MD behind-the-scenes
MD
behind-the-scenes
You mean that MD
The windbreaker
was decided by me
I didn't
do that
What
are you talking about
Ah
the phrase on the back
It's not that I did it all myself
the phrase was already there
They had a phrase prepared
but umm
honestly
there was a lot of talk
about the MD quality
and I also felt a bit
disappointed looking at it
So
we couldn't change things
like the material
anymore
but they said
we could edit
some of the details
inside the design
like the text
and things
like that
so they told us we could edit the details
So to make it a bit more hip
and comfortable
to wear
since it looks a bit weird
to just have the team name right there
you know
Ah so I suggested
filling it up
and writing it out long
like this
Just about that much
And maybe changing the font a bit
Yeah just that much but look
It wasn't some huge idea
it was really just that much
But
I saw it in person too
and it actually came out
quite large
so I think it'll be comfortable
to wear
I also like oversized fits
so I think it'll be pretty
Ah it looks really big when you see it
But when you wear it
it's not ridiculously
huge like
oh this is too big
I can't wear this
It's not like that
It's really
kind of
I don't know the fit looked really pretty to me
I really liked it
Staff members in the 160cm range
wore it
and said it was fine
so we approved
that version
I think it'll be fine
Mmm
If you don't like things too big it might not look pretty
I'm sleepy Flover
I'm sleepy
now
I guess the blood sugar
spike
came
It came too fast
Ah 43 minutes
It's been 43 minutes
Right
The sugar spike came really fast
Ah
I'm slowing down right now
Honestly today
a public fansign right but
we had
since it had been a while
everyone was nervous
I guess
In the car
we all fell into a deep
sleep and then met at the practice room
and everyone had a face
that looked like they just woke up from a deep sleep
Totally
I even drooled a little
that looked like they just woke up from a deep sleep
When I woke up
there was a bit of drool
and then we practiced
and came here
Ah you heard a motorcycle sound
The soundproofing here isn't great
And it might not be
a motorcycle
There's a car here
and its
engine sound
is kind of like that
When it gets to be night time
it sounds a bit like a sports car
making that sound
It used to
keep me up at night
when I first moved in
because of that engine sound
But now I'm used to it so I didn't even notice it just now
It's fine now
Right I'm sleepy
Ah
Should we have cutie time
What should I do buljip bread
Agung bread
What is
melon bread
Melon bread
is a melon
How is it
Salt bread
Choco bread
What would choco bread look like
Maybe
this kind of feeling
A feeling of chocolate
being stuck in there
Soboro bread Soboro bread is kind of
ah
this kind of feeling
Bungeoppang Ah Bungeoppang is
kind of
oh my
this kind of feeling
Mo
cha bun
Ah mocha bun is this too but
mocha bun is huge
like this
Bungeoppang
Memory
test maybe
Anyway
Flover
Thank you so much
for spending my late-night snack time with me today
The public fansign was really fun
I love you
sleep well
Bye bye
See you again
The train is
leaving
I am leaving
Don't hold onto me